swim.com 2011-06-06

# Privacy | iSport.com

By using or accessing [www.iSport.com](http://www.isport.com/) (the “Site”), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. [iSport.com](http://www.isport.com/) (110 Rio Robles, San Jose, California 95134) has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal, signifying that this privacy policy — which contains the company’s practices — has been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html). These requirements include transparency, accountability, and choice regarding the use of your personal information. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [customerservice@isport.com](mailto:customerservice@isport.com). If you are not satisfied with our response, you can contact [TRUSTe](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program only covers information that is collected through this website. It does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site. 

## The Information We Collect

When you visit the Site, you provide us with two types of information: Personal information you knowingly choose to disclose, and information that we collect automatically as you interact with our Site. 

When you sign up to iSport, you provide us with your name, email, gender, and birth date. During the registration process, we give you the opportunity to provide additional profile information, such as where you went to school, your favorite sports, your cell phone number, the languages you speak, and a place to upload photos and videos. There are some cases where we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide you with specific services. Once you register, you can visit your profile at any time to add or remove personal information. 

We cannot control what other users do with your information, so please use common sense regarding the information you include in your profile and provide to other users. Review your profile settings carefully. When you publish content or information using the “Display to Everyone” setting, it means that everyone, including people who are not members of iSport, can access that information. 

We also collect information from you automatically. For example: When you enter the Site, we automatically collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered from all who visit the Site. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer to enable our systems to recognize your computer and provide you with certain features. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies. It will also tell you how to get notification from the browser when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-ons settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, however, we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

We use Google Analytics, a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about our visitors. This is done in order to capture statistics on collective usage and volume. Some of our business partners (e.g., Google Analytics) use cookies on our site. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [iSport.com](http://www.isport.com/) only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party service. 

When you use the Site, you may set up a personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, and transmit information through various channels. The Site may also collect information about you from other sources — such as blogs and instant-messaging services — as well as other users of the Site. We will list you in our publicly accessible member directory. If you do not want to be listed in our directory, contact us at [customerservice@isport.com](mailto:customerservice@isport.com). 

As more fully stated in the “Terms of Use” page, you submit content to the Site at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee: (1) that the content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons; or (2) that those who view your content (whether authorized or not) will not misuse it. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or if other users have copied or stored your content. 

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on the Site is a violation of our Terms of Use and should be reported via our Contact Form. 

## Use of Information Obtained by Us

The information that we collect — from what you tell us and what we gather automatically — is used for one or more of the following general purposes: 

  * To customize the content you see
  * To improve our services
  * To tell you about products or services that may be of interest to you
  * To contact you
  * To conduct advertising and research.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

## Communications from the Site

We may occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions on our site. Out of respect for your privacy, we present you the option to not receive this type of information. To opt out of receiving this type of information, contact us via the feedback option that is always displayed along the far left of your screen toward the top of the page. 

You can invite others to be members of our site by importing contacts from email address books. We use the username and password of the email account from which you wish to import your contacts only to invite new members to the Site. 

## Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

We sometimes release user information on an aggregated basis (meaning that the information from many iSport users is grouped in a way that does not disclose the personal information of any particular user). 

If you choose to create a profile or submit information for inclusion on the Site, this information will, in fact, be available to users of the Site. 

If the ownership of our business changes, either completely or substantially, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the Site can continue to operate. 

Furthermore, in certain situations described below, we will provide your personally identifying information to third parties: 

  * We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. For example, we may use third parties to host the Site, to send out email updates about the Site, to send you targeted advertising, or to remove repetitive information from our user lists. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use in connection with these business activities. 
  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, protect our interests or property, or prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Site or using our name. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, or government agencies. 
  * We may offer products or services jointly with other companies and individuals using the Site. (Collectively, these may be referred to as the “Third-Party Providers.”) You understand and agree that if you use the Site to connect with a Third-Party Provider, we may share your information with the applicable Third-Party Provider to facilitate your transaction. 
  * When you ask us to invite a friend to join iSport, we will send your friend a message on your behalf using your name. If you choose to use our referral service (called “Invite Friends” on the Site), we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. iSport stores this information for the purposes of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [customerservice@isport.com](mailto:customerservice@isport.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

Please note that because the third parties described above operate independently from iSport, iSport bears no responsibility for the activities of any of these third parties with regard to their privacy and security policies. 

By using or accessing the Site, you consent to the disclosures described above. It is iSport's policy to not distribute any personally identifying information about you to third parties without your consent (usually communicated through either an “opt-out” or “opt-in” notification or mechanism), except as otherwise explicitly set forth in this privacy policy. 

## General Privacy Information

You can use the Site to share information with other users and communicate directly with them. iSport may also make various public forums (such as message boards, chat rooms or news groups) available to its users. Please use common sense about the personal information you disclose to others. You are solely responsible for any postings you make on public forums on iSport, and for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you use the Site. 

Furthermore, [iSport.com](http://www.isport.com/) may contain links to partners, advertisers and third-party websites and services that may collect data. iSport may also be linked to by, and in some cases framed by, certain partner websites. Each of the websites (linked from iSport, or linking to iSport) will have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of iSport, and iSport has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site. 

You can link to our site using social-networking services, such as Facebook & Twitter. These services allow you to share information about your activities on iSport. They will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information, such as your name and email address, in order to link between the sites. 

## Changing or Removing Information

You can review and modify most of your personal information at any time by accessing your account. Also, upon your request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove you and your personal information from the Site. Removed information may persist in backup or archived copies, but will not be generally available to the users of the Site or other third parties. 

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and in storage of your data. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100-percent secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [customerservice@isport.com](mailto:customerservice@isport.com). 

## Children Ages 13 through 17

Minors age 13 or older can use the Site only in conjunction with, and under the supervision of, a parent or guardian who has agreed to the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. 

## Children under Age 13

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under age 13, please do not use this Site or send any information about yourself to us. This information includes your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn of collected personal information from a person under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a person under the age of 13, please contact us at [customerservice@isport.com](mailto:customerservice@isport.com). 

## Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of the Site, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions, including limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

## Contacting the Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [customerservice@isport.com](mailto:customerservice@isport.com) or by post mail: 

iSport Customer Service

110 Rio Robles

San Jose, California 95134
